{
    "subject": "resource/Eil\u00eds_Dillon",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Galway",
    "human_readable": "Eil\u00eds Dillon was born in Galway.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.92159503698349,
            "question": "Where was Eil\u00eds Dillon born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106683731079102,
            "question": "In what country was Eil\u00eds Dillon born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9023265838623047,
            "question": "Name the city where Eil\u00eds Dillon was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5897714495658875,
            "question": "What is Eil\u00eds Dillon known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4531559944152832,
            "question": "Was Eil\u00eds Dillon an Irish author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37445080280303955,
            "question": "What type of work did Eil\u00eds Dillon do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2880522608757019,
            "question": "What is Galway known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25335004925727844,
            "question": "Can you name one of Eil\u00eds Dillon's most popular works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22215799987316132,
            "question": "What genre of writing did Eil\u00eds Dillon specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21441419422626495,
            "question": "Did Eil\u00eds Dillon write any famous books?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eil\u00eds Dillon was born in Galway.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8680_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of writing did Eil\u00eds Dillon specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8680_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name one of Eil\u00eds Dillon's most popular works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8680_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Galway known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8680_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8680_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context documents confirm that Eil\u00eds Dillon was indeed born in Galway, which aligns with the query statement. Document 62 and 7 both mention her birthplace as Galway, County Galway on March 7, 1920. Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Eil\u00eds Dillon's birthplace, stating that she was born in Galway. Therefore, the statement \"Eil\u00eds Dillon was born in Galway\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}